## **Bryn Bennett**



+64 275215835



http://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

#### About me —

I am a fourth-year Software Engineering student at Victoria University. Some of my other passions include: yachting, canoe polo, skiing, and gaming. As well as spending a large amount of time completing university projects I have undertaken and worked on some of my own personal projects and balance this with spending time training for national and international regattas as part of the Wellington Youth Sailing Trust Match Racing Squad.

# Skills -Angular Firebase **HTML** CSS React Git Java CSharp

## Language & Frameworks

















### Education

BE(Hons) converted to B.Sc in 2019 2016 - 2019

Majoring in Computer Science

NCEA: Level 1, 2, and 3 with Excellence 2010 - 2015 Rongotai College

Web Technology and Programming, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry,

Victoria University

Geography, English, Economics

### Work Experience

#### 2019 - present Development Squad Coach

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- · Coaching a group of 6 teenagers
  - Setting out a season training plan for the squad
  - · Adapting trainings for the conditions and what the sailors will find the most beneficial

#### **Software Development of Employment Website** 2018

Pihinga

- · Designed and developed a job search platform for solo
- Managing development of the project from start to finish as part of a group of six
- Requirement gathering through client interaction
- · Balancing client wants with what is feasible with the given time constraints.

#### 2018 - present Web App Development For the Following Yacht Clubs

Tup Radford Intercollegiate Yachting Academy, Queen Charlotte Yacht Club, New Plymouth Yacht Club

 Adaptation of a previously developed web app to the requirements of a different set of clients

#### 2017 - present Yacht & Power Boat Maintenance Technician

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- Maintenance of small keel boats and a rigid inflatable boat
- Identifying what work is most important and allocating time accordingly
- Prioritising work around upcoming events the boats will be
- · Purchasing spare parts and reporting to monthly trust meetings

#### 2017 - present Web App Development For Youth Sailing Program

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- Designed and developed a web and mobile accessible app for tracking boat maintenance issues, and health and safety documentation
- · Researching existing tools and frameworks to help the development of a web app
- Understanding Maritime New Zealand's requirements and the Marine Operators Safety System (MOSS)
- Identifying and communicating the benefits introducing the system would have on the trusts processes

### 2013 - present Junior and Adult Learn to Sail Coach

Worser Bay Boating Club

- Coaching students of all ages and skill levels
- · Tailoring sessions to the students and how they learn, practical and theory
- · Catering for what the student wants from the course: confidence in a boat, ability to race, just having fun



2017 Blind Foundation - 'Have a go sailing day'
2017, 2018 Wellington Marathon - Drink Stations
2015, 2016 Wellington Marathon - Marshal

## Bryn Bennett

+64 275215835



http://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

Skills -

Angular

Firebase

HTML

CSS

React

Git

Java

CSharp

## Language & Frameworks

















## Awards

2017 Facult	ty of Engineering Deans List	Victoria University
2016 Excell	ence Scholarship	Victoria University
2015 <b>Schoo</b>	ol Prize Digital Technologies	Rongotai College
2013 - 2015 <b>Schoo</b>	ol Honours Awards for Yachting	Rongotai College

## Other Qualifications

2018	NZTA - Advanced Driving Skills
2017	Yachting New Zealand - Learn to Sail Coach
2016	St John - CPR & Basic First Aid
2013	Yachting New Zealand - Assistant Learn to Sail Coach
Sporting	Achievements

2019	NZ Youth Match Racing Worlds Trials - 2nd (crew of 4)
2019	Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 3rd
	(crew of 4)
2018	Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 2nd
	(crew of 4)
2017	Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th
	(crew of 5)
2016	Nespresso Youth Match Racing - 3rd (crew of 5)
2016	Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 3rd
	(crew of 4)
2016	Musto Intérnational Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 5th
	(crew of 5)
2016	Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th
	(crew of 5)
2014	NZ Youth Match Racing Nationals - 1st and National Champion
	(crew of 4)
2014	Nespresso Youth Match Racing Regatta - 1st (crew of 5)
2013	College Sport Wellington Regional Canoe Polo Champion
	(team of 7)
2013	NZ Laser 4.7 Nationals - 1st and National Champion